yellowpages.co.in 2015-06-15

# Infomedia Yellow Pages, India's No 1 Yellow Pages Directory with 50000+ Trusted & Verified Business

## Infomedia Yellow Pages Privacy Policy

### We take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy

Infomedia Yellow Pages is an online local search service that helps people find relevant providers of products and services in their locality, area, or city. To accomplish this, our users add listings that are posted to the Infomedia Yellow Pages Site. These listings can then be accessed and read by other Infomedia Yellow Pages users. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, a "user" is defined as someone using and accessing the Infomedia Yellow Pages Site. You should visit this page periodically to review any changes to the Privacy Policy.

#### 1\. Information We Collect

When you visit this Website, Infomedia18 may collect the following types of information: 

  * Personally Identifiable Information You Knowingly Provide
  * Information Infomedia18 Collects Automatically
  * Non-Personally Identifiable Information You Knowingly Provide

Infomedia18 collects personally identifiable information that you knowingly provide to us. For example, Infomedia18 may ask you to provide personally identifiable contact information (such as name, address, e-mail address and telephone number). If you purchase a product or service, Infomedia18 may ask you to provide additional information including photos, videos, menus and catalogs and/or description of your products and services, your credit card information, . Infomedia18 may also ask you to provide other information such as a personal ID, password, security question and answer, and birthday etc. You are responsible for the accuracy and completeness of all personally identifiable information that you knowingly provide.

In addition, as you (and other users) browse This Website, our web servers automatically collect certain information about such visits (usually through the use of cookies, JavaScript tags, clear .gif files --also known as "web beacons"-- and the analysis of http headers and other technology), such as the user's IP address, the user's domain name, the user's browser type, the user's user agent, how many users visit This Website, which pages the user visits and for how long, the date and time the user accesses This Website, the Internet address of the site from which the user directly linked to This Website and the links on This Website on which the user clicks. In addition, Infomedia18 may collect certain search parameters relating to searches conducted by the user which are not entered by the user.

In some cases, we may also collect non-personally identifiable information that you provide, such as search parameters in connection with a search you conduct through This Website, ratings and reviews, and zip code. 

To improve the services we can offer you, we may decide to expand This Website's capabilities for obtaining information about users in the future. 

#### 2\. How We Use Your Information

Your full name and email address may be used when sharing business listing information with your friends. We may also use your email address to send you updates or news regarding our site, but you may choose not to receive email of this type by sending us a postal mail mentioning your email address at _Infomedia Yellow Pages Unsubscribe C/o Infomedia 18, 'A' Wing, Ruby House, JK Sawant Marg, Dadar (W), Mumbai 400028_. Browser-type related information, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp data help us diagnose problems with our server, administer Infomedia Yellow Pages, and otherwise provide the highest possible level of service to you. In addition, we use this information to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the site and to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of users that have been exposed to or clicked on, their advertising banners.

#### 3\. Transfer of Information

Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your personal information. Infomedia 18 will disclose information about individual users to governmental or judicial authorities or law enforcement agencies, or to other individuals or entities in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal processes. Further, Infomedia 18 may share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities or suspected fraud, or to enforce or apply the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event of a transfer of ownership of Infomedia Yellow Pages, such as an acquisition by or merger with another company. In such an event, Infomedia 18 will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. Infomedia 18 will notify you when information about you may be provided to third parties in ways other than explained above, and you will have the option to prevent such information sharing.

#### 4\. Links

Our website may contain links to third party websites to which we have no affiliation. Infomedia 18 does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on these third party websites.

#### 5\. Use of Cookies

Like most websites, Infomedia Yellow Pages requires cookies to function properly. Cookies are small text files that reside on a user's computer and identify you as a unique user. We use cookies to refine our site and simplify the user experience. For example, the use of cookies allows registered users to enter our site without explicitly typing in their email address and password every time. You should be aware that Infomedia Yellow Pages cannot control the use of cookies by advertisers or any information advertisers may gather from their use of cookies. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, you should note that cookies may be necessary to provide you certain features (e.g., customized delivery of information) available on the Infomedia Yellow Pages site.

#### 6\. Controlling Your Personal Information

As a registered Infomedia Yellow Pages user, you can modify your personal information at any time by accessing the "Account" section of the site. Also, upon your request, Infomedia 18 will use commercially reasonable efforts to functionally remove you and your personal information from the site; however, it may be impossible to remove your entry without some residual information being retained by Infomedia 18. Registered users who wish to close their account should contact [iypconnect@infomedia18.in](mailto:iypconnect@infomedia18.in).

#### 7\. Security

Your Infomedia Yellow Pages account is password-protected. Infomedia 18 tries very hard to protect our users' information. We use industry standard measures to protect your information that is stored within our database. We limit the access to your information to those employees who need access to perform their job function such as our customer service personnel. If you have any questions about the security at our website, please contact us. Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. You hereby acknowledge that Infomedia 18 is not responsible for any intercepted information sent via the Internet, and you hereby release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of intercepted information in any unauthorized manner.

#### 8\. Emails and Opt-out

At this time, registered members may opt-out of receiving notifications initiated by Infomedia Yellow Pages by sending us a postal mail mentioning your email address at _Infomedia Yellow Pages Unsubscribe C/o Infomedia 18, 'A' Wing, Ruby House, JK Sawant Marg, Dadar (W), Mumbai 400028_. Unregistered users that do not wish to receive emails may opt-out of receiving any communications by following the instructions contained in all emails.

#### 9\. Children

This website is not directed to children, and Infomedia 18 does not knowingly solicit information from any child under the age of 13. Should a child whom we know to be under 13 send personal information to us, we will use that information only to respond directly to that child (or a parent or guardian) to inform him or her that we must have parental consent before receiving his or her personal information.

#### 10\. Terms and Modifications to this Privacy Statement

By using the website, you signify your agreement to the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with these terms, you should not use the site. Infomedia 18 may modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If a material change is made to this Privacy Policy and/or the way we use our users' personally identifiable information, then we will post a prominent notice of the nature of such change on the first page of this Privacy Policy and also on our home page. You are responsible for reviewing this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes to it. Your continued use of the site indicates your assent to any changes to this Privacy Policy.

#### 11\. Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the privacy practices of this website, or if you want to exercise any of the rights that you are given under this Privacy Policy, you can contact: Infomedia 18, 'A' Wing, Ruby House, JK Sawant Marg, Dadar (W), Mumbai 400028.
